In the Forecast Fragment class, we add the callback
that was provided in the gist. Then in the onCreateView
method, we modify the item click behavior. When an
item is clicked, we move the cursor to that position
and then we read out the date string. We
call getActivity and then we cast it to a Callback
object. And then we call onItemSelected, with that date
string. Then in the MainActivity, we implement this Callback interface.
In the onItemSelected method, we fork behavior based on
the TwoPane variable that we defined earlier. If we're
in TwoPane mode, then we create a new DetailFragment
using the date in the arguments bundle. And then
we replace the existing fragment in the weather_detail_container. Otherwise,
in OnePane mode, we create a new intent to
launch the detail activity setting the date as an
intent extra. In the detail activity, we modify the onCreate
method to read the intent extras from the intent that
came from the main activity. We take this date and set
it in the arguments bundle to initialize the detail fragment.
And we dynamically add the detail fragment to this container. In
the detail fragment, we modify the on create loader method
to read from the arguments that were passed in. We get
the date string out and use it with the location
string to build up the Uri to query the content provider.
We also remove any reliance on the incoming intent.
We switch it to use the arguments bundle, instead. For
example, in the onActivityCreated method, we only initialize the loader
if the arguments is not null. In the onResume method,
we also modify the condition so that it checks that
the arguments bundle is not null. When you try it
out on the tablet, there is one bug related to
navigation that we should fix. Say we select tomorrows date.
If you navigate to the settings activity and then hit
the up button, the detail fragment is blank. That's because
a brand new instance of main activity got launched and
for a brand new instance, nothing is selected yet. To fix
this, when the settings activity up button is pressed, we
want to navigate to the previous running instance of the
main activity, where the tomorrow item is selected. And not
create a new instance of main activity. In the settings activity,
overwrite this method. Which the system will call in
order to get the parent activity intent for the up
button behaviour. Get the parent activity intent from the
super class, this should create a new intent to main
activity. Then add the intent flag, called FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_TOP. This
flag indicates that we should check if the main activity
is already running in our task. And to use
that one, instead of creating a new main activity instance.
Also, this method didn't exist prior to jelly bean, so we need
to add this at target API annotation. If you check the documentation
for the activity class, the getParentActivityIntent method was only added in API
level 16. And you can check that version 16 maps to jelly bean.